hellokpop.com 2018-10-11

# Privacy Policy | hellokpop

**Who we are**

Our website address is: https://www.hellokpop.com.

The term “personal data” as used in this Policy refers to personally identifiable information such as your name, birth date, email address, mailing address, etc. that can be used to identify you. We are committed to protecting your privacy on the internet. We will treat any information that we receive from you with care and recognize the need for appropriate action to manage and protect any information that you share with us.

**What personal data we collect and why we collect it  
**  
Our services on this Website do not require any form of direct registration, allowing you to visit and browse our site without disclosing your identity to us. However, some services and social media services may require registration and logging in before using it. When you register or log in with us or the social media services provided, you may need to provide to our Website with your personal data. In other situations, we may also have received your personally identifiable information through our Website feedback form or when you send us an electronic mail message. In these situations, the personal data shall only be used for the purpose for which you gave it to us. Our Website does not collect information or create individual profiles for commercial marketing.

In all situations, we will keep your personal data only for as long as is reasonably needed for the purposes that it is provided to us and in accordance with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or documentation retention requirements.

**Non-Disclosure of Information  
**  
We will not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your personal data to third parties outside hellokpop.com. However, personal data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for or on behalf of hellokpop, for further processing in accordance with the purpose(s) for which the data were originally collected. Where disclosure of personal data to a third party is likely or necessary for whatever reason, we will, wherever possible, endeavor to ensure that the disclosure and intended use of the data are clearly indicated. Such third parties may operate different privacy policies. However, we endeavour to ensure that such third parties provide the same level of protection as hellokpop and, where appropriate, we will contractually require them to process data transferred only for the purposes expressly authorized by hellokpop.

**Security and Confidentiality  
**  
To ensure the security and confidentiality of personal data that we collect online, we use data networks protected, inter- alias, by industry standard firewall and password protection. If an internal employee breaches our policies and procedures, he/she will be disciplined accordingly. Staff compliance with our policies and procedures is regularly reviewed. While we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse or alteration to data, we try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences to the best of our ability at all times.

**Gathering of Anonymous Data  
**  
Most of the information that www.hellokpop.com collects from its Website is anonymous information, such as the pages you visit and searches you perform. When you visit our Website, we do not collect any personal data from you. Anonymous information is processed by us to help improve the contents of the Website and to compile aggregate statistics about individuals using our site for internal analysis purposes only.

**Spamming**

We do not condone “spamming”. Spamming is defined as sending unsolicited e-mails, usually of a commercial nature, in large numbers and repeatedly to individuals with whom the sender has had no previous contact or who have declined to receive such communications. We also have user comment moderation policies in place to prevent user spamming.

**Links to Other Sites  
**  
This Privacy Policy applies only to www.hellokpop.com to the exclusion of third party websites. We may provide links to other/or partner websites which we believe may be of interest to our visitors. We aim to ensure that such websites are of the highest standard. However, due to the nature of the World Wide Web, we cannot guarantee the standards of every website link it provides or be responsible for the contents of external sites.

**Google’s Use Of Data**

Read:[How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

**Contact hellokpop**

For any queries, recommendations or comments to improve the quality of our Privacy Policy, please contact the [webmaster](https://www.hellokpop.com/contact-us/). We aim to constantly improve the tools available to you to manage the data that you provide to us. Please refer to this page from time to time to review any updates which concerns your personal interest.

**Disclaimer**

Read: [Our disclaimer on linked content, intellectual property, rights and responsibilities, opinionated contents (editorials, reviews), comment policy and contest rules](https://www.hellokpop.com/disclaimer/)

**Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site, we collect the data shown in the comment form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

**Cookies**

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

**Embedded content from other websites**  
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**How long we retain your data**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

**What rights you have over your data**

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
